<!--
  ~ Copyright (C) 2016 Krishna Patait
  ~
  ~ Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  ~ you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
  ~ You may obtain a copy of the License at
  ~
  ~    http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
  ~
  ~ Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  ~ distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  ~ WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  ~ See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  ~ limitations under the License.
  -->

<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Traffic App</string>
    <string name="intro_text">Point the camera view to a QR Code to read the information</string>
    <string name="restart_activity">Restart Activity</string>
    <string name="stop_start_qreader">Stop QREader</string>
    <string name="action_add_favourite">Add to Favourites</string>
    <string name="action_play_next">Play Next</string>
    <string name="spinner_title">Select Document Type</string>
    <string name="spinner_vtype">Select Vehicle Type</string>
    <string name="spinner_vcolor">Select Vehicle Color</string>
    <string name="backdrop_title">LOVE MUSICS</string>
    <string name="yes1">CASH COLLECTED</string>

    <string name="backdrop_subtitle">This season top 20 music</string>
    <string name="preface_english">"Download Traffic Pune App and make commuting safe and simple in the following ways:

 Find out which roads are blocked for road repairs, processions or other public events. Find out what alternative routes are planned.

 Not sure what the traffic rules are, or how much fine you should pay for a particular offence? Traffic Pune App provides the right answer.

 Pune Traffic Police is committed to the use of latest technology in the service of its citizens.

 For any proposed changes in the traffic plan in your locality, send in your opinions and suggestions online.

 Propose fresh changes and ideas and contribute to traffic safety in your locality.

 View contact numbers for senior traffic officials in case of emergency.

 Report accidents, traffic problems and emergencies in your locality and receive quick police assistance.

 During rains and in other special conditions, find out where the traffic bottlenecks are.

 Traffic Pune App provides a bridge between traffic police and citizens for instant, proactive and interactive communication.

 Jai Hind !

 Pune Traffic Police"</string>
    <string name="title_activity_upload_img">Upload User Document</string>
    <string name="title_activity_activity__user__registration">User Registration</string>
    <string name="title_activity_police_dash_borad">PoliceDashBorad</string>


    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="single_permission_text">(Click on FAB to check Single permission.\nTo test again, change the app permission in settings or reinstall the app)</string>
</resources>
